<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Caleb Key</title>
    <link>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Caleb Key</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:02:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Calebstone</title>
      <link>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/calebstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:02:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/calebstone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Developed a card-based strategy card game featuring a Godot frontend and Flask backend, enhanced with reinforcement learning models that allow AI agents to autonomously play against each other.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDR</title>
      <link>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/hdr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:02:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/hdr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Built a digit recognition system with a custom neural network from scratch, achieving 95% accuracy on the MNIST dataset. Included a Tkinter-based UI for real-time digit drawing and inference.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandas</title>
      <link>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/pandas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:02:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/pandas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It can be a bit overwhelming how ubiquitous AI has become in everyday conversations. When I first started studying AI at Texas A&amp;amp;M, part of the excitement was that it felt like an &amp;ldquo;up-and-coming&amp;rdquo; field, even though, looking back, the signs were already clear that the technology was primed to explode, leading directly to the boom we saw in 2023. You might assume someone beginning their career in AI would feel thrilled that nearly every company is eager to brand itself as an &amp;ldquo;AI company,&amp;rdquo; but truthfully, I miss the simpler days when everyone wasn&amp;rsquo;t talking about whether computers are &amp;ldquo;alive.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cache Optimization via GA</title>
      <link>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/ga/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 08:28:40 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://calebkey121.github.io/blogs/ga/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Texas A&amp;amp;M, I wanted to get an undergraduate research credit and the only way I knew how was by finding a professor to sponsor you. I remember searching the staff directory for anyone with &amp;lsquo;AI&amp;rsquo; tied to their research and did a cold call email to 20 profs. Two responded and one took me on and I was introduced to the world of research. I definitely felt out of my league, but I think this is the point of this experience so that you have an understanding of the work it takes to publish a paper. My task was to utilize genetic algorithms to explore the problem space that they were studying, and while I don&amp;rsquo;t really think that my project was groundbreaking, I think it was the perfect learning project to become familiar with GAs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
